So, hello everyone, in this video, we are going to work with our get messages controller.
So, let's start this.
So, export, so export, const, send messages, send messages, again we are going to just give
this as async and then request response as we have get earlier.
And now after this, what we are actually going to do is, since the sender can, like send
any format of, like text or image, so we are going to get that, okay.
But before that, we are going to use this try and cache block, okay, declare this try
and cache block and when this, this cache block, we will have this error, okay.
So now inside of the, whatever the logic or the code, we are going to write inside of our
try block and with the cache block, we are going to just cache the error, whatever it comes, okay.
So the first thing would be, D structure, whatever the text or the image, which is going
to come, so text comma image equal to request dot body from the body, we are parsing the
text and image, D structuring the image and now, who has sent the image, so we are going
to just declare one sender ID, sender ID and the sender ID, we are going to just get it
from the request dot user dot underscore ID.
And now, after the sender ID, we will have the receiver ID, see, receiver ID, we are going
to get this receiver ID from the params, okay.
So params dot underscore ID.
Now, after this, let's declare one image URL, we are, we are going to store the image,
whatever it is sent by the sender or the receiver.
So if an image comes, okay, so if the image comes, in that case, we are going to just
store this in the upload image variable and for this one, we are going to use the cloud
inary.
So cloudinary dot uploader dot, sorry, uploader cloud nine dot uploader dot, we are going
to use the upload function, so upload and then we are going to pass this image as here
and now, for the image URL, we are going to just take that image from the upload image
and store it inside it, so secure dot URL.
So for this image part is done, now comes the part for the message.
What will happen if the sender just sends the message, okay, in that case, we are going
to destructure it like we're going to get all the message part, like whatever there is
it in message, okay, so message, so const message equal to new messages and after this,
we are going to take the sender ID, we are going to take the receiver ID and we are also
going to take the, take the text as well as we are going to take any kind of image that
has been thrown, so image URL from this image URL, we are going to take and pass this
in the message, all right, so now we are going to just save this, so await, await, new
message dot save, we are going to save this new message and after this, if the new message
does so, new message, if this new message is existing, we are going to return the status,
so response of data status 200, so 200, one, we are going to just send the JSON, JSON as
new message, and inside the message, new message, we are going to just pass this as new
message, okay, so now we have completed this, I think there's some kind of issue here,
so in the JSON, just pass this as new message, okay, so the new message and now in the
cache lock, what we are going to do is console.log console.log and if the error persist,
so if the error exist, then in the send message would be error in send message controller,
okay, and we are going to send the message out, so error dot message, right, and after
this, we are going to throw an error using the status code of rys dot status dot 500 dot
JSON, and instead of this, we will have this message put, and we will just say that it
is a internal server error, alright, so now we have completed this send messages controller,
what the send message is controller, let's go to this route part, okay, so there would
be one route, so now route dot get, and then we are going to get this send messages, and
with this we are also going to implement this check auth, so the send messages will also
have one particular associated id, right, so id, then check auth, and then with this part
we will have this as send messages, so control and save, which should be working fine,
so now we have worked with the send messages, I am going to meet you in the next video.